前情提要
「移花接木」 是一种实时图像处理的方法
Correction is a method of real time image manipulation,
通过干扰摄像头信号的深度伪造技术来实现
using the disruption of camera feeds and the deployment of deep-fake technology.
所以我的遭遇 它还有个名字
So it has a name, what happened to me?
瑞秋绝对给特纳留下了好印象
Rachel certainly made an impression on Turner.
取得他的支持难道不好吗
Wouldn't hurt to keep him on side.
你好像忘了 她差点就要举报我们了
You seem to forget how close she came to reporting us.
你要是还信不过她 吉玛 你知道该怎么做
If you still don't trust her, Gemma, you know what to do.
看好她
Keep her close.
我录下这段视频留档
I'm filming this for my dossier,
里面详细记录了系统性的非法篡改视频证据的行为
detailing the systematic, illegal practice of video evidence tampering
被称为「移花接木」
known as Correction.
如果你需要对付BBC的技术支持 我借给你人
If you need technical help with the BBC, I'll loan you one of my guys.
但如果我发现你让他参与针对中国的行动 交易取消
But if I find out you put them on China, the deal's off.
你确信是中国的手笔
You're convinced China's responsible?
北京要干预英国的政策
Beijing is trying to meddle in British policy.
严王磊是赞达在伦敦的老大
Yan Wanglei, Xanda's man in London,
他绝对参与其中了
he's a part of it. I'm certain.
有时我觉得似乎有两个艾萨克·特纳
Sometimes to seems to me as if there are two Isaac Turners.
我到底应该相信哪个艾萨克·特纳呢
So which Isaac Turner should I believe?
作为赞达面部识别的伦敦首席执行官
As London's CEO of Xanda Facial Rec,
严王磊具备动机和技术能力
Yan Wanglei has the motive and the technical capability.
你们警长的遭遇我很难过
I'm sorry to hear about your detective sergeant.
你说他中枪了 但没说他活下来没有
You he was shot but you didn't say if he survived.
我是没说
No, I didn't.
你愿意加入监视组吗
How do you feel about joining the surveillance unit?
我们需要人盯梢严王磊
We need eyes on Yan Wanglei.
愿意 长官
Sir.
帕特里克 你一定要醒过来
Patrick, you'd better wake up.
我们需要你
We need you.
不 我不是加入了他们
No, I haven't joined them.
我是要打败他们
I am trying to beat them.
他们日夜不停的监视着我
And they are watching me day and night.
艾萨克·特纳刚甩掉了他的安保人员
Isaac Turner's just cut his protection officers loose.
他今晚要上《新闻之夜》
He's booked himself on Newsnight.
特纳先生
Mr Turner!
为了保护秘密 他们不惜杀人
They kill people to protect it.
难不成你有曝光的计划
Have you got a plan to expose it?
您改变主意了吗
Have you changed your mind?
我已决定推荐内阁...
I've reached my decision to recommend to the cabinet...
...将定性视为人工智能的缺陷 但在赞达这里是卖点
..see profiling as an AI flaw. Xanda treats it as a selling point.
快把节目掐断
Somebody stop this broadcast!
怎么切不断
It's not cutting!
我提倡在涉及国民安全的领域使用种族定性
I'm advocating the use of racial profiling wherever it keeps us safe.
我们被黑了
We've been hacked.
这是伪造的
This has been changed, faked.
被「移花接木」过
Corrected.
你需要切实证明这件事
You need to prove it definitively,
实锤定音
so no-one can deny it.
你有什么建议吗
And how do you suggest doing that?
和我一起
Together.
我刚在电视直播中断送了自己的职业生涯
I've just committed career suicide on live TV.
可并不是我干的
Except I haven't.
怎么 你们还想让我保持沉默吗
And...what? I'm expected to stay silent?
我老婆觉得我疯了
My wife thinks I've gone insane,
我员工威胁要辞职
my staff are threatening to quit
内政大臣也不接我电话了
and the Home Secretary's stopped answering my calls.
我知道这对你来说很艰难
I understand how difficult this must be.
哦 是吗
Oh, oh, do you?
因为在镜头前为种族偏见大唱赞歌的可不是你
Because last time I looked it wasn't you on camera extolling the virtues of racial bias.
你不是说他很配合吗
I thought you said he was being cooperative?
毕竟发生了这么多事
All things considered.
也许我没资格给你分析利害
Perhaps it's not my place to remind you of the stakes.
不用了
No need.
你的小跟班已经解释过不配合的恶果了
Your minion explained it to us on pain of death.
事关国家安全
Issues of National Security,
那些我们永远不可能知道或理解的事
the likes of which we can never know or understand.
感谢你的支持
I appreciate your support.
毕竟我们都是国家公仆
We're all public servants, eh?
我只能把自己干疮百孔的信心寄托在你们身上
And I shall just have to cling to my much tested belief
相信这一切都是为了国家利益最大化
that you people have the nation's best interests at heart,
并假设你们会尽最大努力
and assume you'll do everything in your power
防止此类事件再次发生
to prevent this ever happening again.
我们需要你回答一些问题 理清事发经过
We'll need you to answer some questions, go over what happened.
可以 但配合你们熬了这么晚
Fine. But as this is past my bedtime,
我需要喝点什么撑下去
I'm going to need a little something to keep me going.
好在我知道艾德的好东西都藏哪儿
Luckily, I know where Ed keeps his stash.
咖啡
Coffee.
有人要喝吗
Anyone else?
谢谢你
Thank you.
奶和糖我就看情况吧
I can't promise milk and sugar.
她看着挺配合
She seems very compliant.
你是怎么说服她的
How the hell did you manage that?
跟你学的 长官
Learning from you, ma'am.
控制台呼叫K1
Control to Kilo 1.
K1收到
Kilo 1.
真相捕捉
第二季  第三集
导致任务失败的最常见原因
Most common cause of compromise.
什么
Sorry?
需要上厕所
Needing a wee.
我不需要
I don't.
你的腿在抖
Your leg is shaking.
我不需要上厕所
I don't need a wee.
想上的话只有一个办法
There's only one option if you do.
我才不要在你车里撒尿
I'm not going to wet myself in your car.
你也不是第一个了
You wouldn't be the first.
有动静
Movement.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
控制台 K9 你说
Control, Kilo 9. Go ahead.
目标出现
Eyes on target.
老大
Guv?
王磊开始移动了
Wanglei is mobile.
必须给我全方位追踪
I want the holy trinity of tracking.
盯梢 面部识别 GPS信号
Eyes on, face rec and GPS.
收到
Sir.
K9 确认目标身份
Confirm eyeball on target, Kilo 9.
确认
Pos ID.
运行面部识别
Run facial rec.
正在进行
Happening.
目标身份确认
Target ID confirmed.
人脸比对确认
Facial Rec confirmed.
进行车牌识别
Run vehicle check.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标开着一辆黑色S系奔驰
Target is in a black S class Mercedes,
车牌号735D812
registration 735D812.
确认
Confirmed.
外交牌照
Diplomatic plates.
看来他有大使馆的庇护
Good to know the Embassy's looking after him.
给我盯住那辆奔驰
Get me into that Merc.
待命 待命
Stand by. Stand by.
目标开始移动
Target on the move.
追踪车辆
Track that vehicle.
K9 尾随目标
Kilo 9, tail target.
K9 跟紧了
Stay close, Kilo 9.
眼睛一刻也别离开
Maintain eyeball on target.
明白
Understood.
K9呼叫控制台 目标在高尔路左转
Kilo 9 to Control. Target turning left on Gower Road.
运行自动车牌识别系统
Run ANPR.
正在运行
Happening.
确认
Confirmed.
调到GPS了吗
How's that GPS?
锁定奔驰的信号了
We're into the Merc.
非常好
Outstanding.
先生
Sir?
有人跟着我们
Somebody is following us.
警察
Cops?
■
这里听不懂，大概这个意思吧
绕下路吧
Let's take a detour.
甩掉他们
Take care of it, will you?
汇报情况 K9
Tell us what you've got, Kilo 9.
目标左转到曼德维尔广场
Target turning left onto Mandeville Place.
确认
Confirmed.
目标停在贝尔维尤路路口
Target held at the junction with Bellevue Road.
确认
Confirmed.
目标刚闯了红灯 跟踪行动暴露
Target just ran a red light. Tail compromised.
控制台呼叫 K9
This is Control to Kilo 9.
我不管目标知不知道你们在跟踪
I don't care if the target knows you're there.
别让他离开你视线
Just don't let him out of your sight.
明白
Understood.
他不想被跟踪
He does not want to be followed.
挺硬气
Tough shit.
英国穆斯林协会发言人今晚早些时候
A spokesperson for the Muslim Council of Great Britain
要求安全大臣艾萨克·特纳
has called on Security Minister Isaac Turner to "apologise or resign"
在做出种族定性人工智能的发言后下台或道歉
after comments he made about racial profiling AI earlier this evening.
大臣的说法荒唐至极 无礼至极
The minister's claims are not just absurd and offensive -
这是煽动性言论
they are inflammatory,
只会让最恶毒的种族刻板印象深入人心
and reinforce the most damaging racial stereotypes.
事实上 正是赞达的种族定性
The truth is racial-profiling is what makes Xanda
才成为市场上最有效的安全系统
the most effective security system on the market.
假设说 当然只是举例
If, say, and I'm not saying this is the case,
但假设说17到35岁的穆斯林男子
but if, say, Muslim men between the ages of 17...
这是爸爸吗
Is it Daddy?
是最有可能对机场发动袭击的群体
..were the most likely demographic to launch an attack on an airport...
不 不是爸爸
No. It wasn't him.
去睡觉吧 哈里森 已经很晚了
Go back to bed, Harrison. It's the middle of the night.
他会回来吗
When is he coming back?
就快回来了 亲爱的
Soon, darling.
去吧 我马上上楼跟你说晚安
Go. I'll come and kiss you night-night in a minute.
■
艾萨克
你什么时候回来
■
要半夜才能回去
哦
■
给我回电
艾萨克 你还好吗
■
现在不方便 再给你回电
申请支援
Call for support.
记录所有人的身份 录口供
I want everyone here ID'd, questioned
给所有人下发国防安全须知令
and slap a D-notice on the whole lot.
就算不是嫌疑人 他们也是目击者
If they're not suspects they're witnesses.
我天啊
Christ.
记者啊
Journos!
最难闭紧嘴巴的一群人
Can't think of worse people to try to keep quiet.
长官 在我看来
Ma'am, from where I was standing,
他们应该并未看到发生了什么
I don't think any of them witnessed it.
他们知道出事儿了
They know something happened
但他们当时的注意力都集中在假视频上
but they were all watching the fake version.
不光是信号源被远程控制了
The whole system was taken over remotely,
整个系统都是
not just the feeds.
包括硬件设施
The hardware.
在控制室中 特纳的画面是锁定的
The edit was locked on Turner in that control room.
掐都掐不断
They couldn't cut away.
把所有能进入房间接触到设备的人 列张单子出来
We need a list of everybody with access to that room, that kit.
这里一定有人是同谋
Somebody here must be complicit.
会不会是汗
What about Khan?
不是
No.
从卡迪加·汗的反应来看 我
Khadija Khan's reaction, I just, erm...
我觉得更有可能是幕后的人干的
I just think somebody behind the scenes is more likely.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
请讲
Kilo 9, go ahead.
目标驶入A4公路
Target joining the A4.
确认
Confirmed.
确认 A4向西行
Confirmed. A4 Westbound.
西行
Westbound.
目标的家庭住址在哪
What's the target's home address?
葛兰许 五橡岭
The Grange, Five Oak Green.
五橡岭他妈在哪儿
Five Oak Green, what the fuck is that?
肯特郡的一个村庄
A village in Kent.
但他没朝那个方向去 不是吗
Well, he's not headed there, is he?
除非他要绕道看风景
Not unless he's taking the scenic route.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标进入M4高速公路
Target joining the M4 Motorway.
确认
Confirmed.
确认 M4向西行
Confirmed. The M4, westbound.
控制台呼叫K1
Control to Kilo 1.
请讲
Go ahead.
嫌疑人在移动
Suspect is on the move.
正朝希思罗机场方向移动
Direction of Heathrow.
检查旅客登记信息
Check passenger logs.
正在检查
Happening.
24小时内飞往北京的航班中 找不到他的名字
No name matches any flights to Beijing in the next 24 hours.
可能用的假身份
Could be travelling under a false ID.
你们说的是王磊吗
You're talking about Wanglei?
不能让他上飞机 K1
We can't let him board a plane, Kilo 1.
我知道 但这是一个政治决策
I'm aware. It's a political decision.
你想通知内政部吗
You want to wake up the Home Sec?
不 不行
No, no.
你想取得政府支持 逮捕中国公民吗
Look, you want Government backing to arrest a Chinese national?
最好由上层 内政大臣或者首相下达命令
Top cover, ideally. Home Sec or PM.
是 等你收到明确答复的时候
Yeah, by the time you get a straight answer the target
目标人物早就飞走了
will be in the air.
你为什么这么说
What makes you say that?
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标正经过M4高速2号匝道
Target passing M4 Junction 2.
-确认 -确认
- Confirmed.  - Confirmed.
15分钟后到达1号航站楼
15 minutes to Terminal 1.
我是安全大臣
I'm the Security Minister.
我就能对重大事件做出决策
I can declare a critical incident.
有我在 干嘛要叫醒吉尔呢
Why wake up Gill when you've got me?
他坐的是外交车辆 我没法截停他
I can't stop him in a diplomatic vehicle.
我知道
I'm aware.
当目标人物显现飞走意图 就实施逮捕
Arrest when target shows intent to travel,
发布全港通告 推迟所有向东飞行的航班
issue an all-ports warning, delay every flight headed east.
只要目标进入出发层就行动
Target steps into Departures, that's good enough for me.
经安全大臣批准 我将前往希思罗机场
I'm heading to Heathrow with a green light from the Security Minister.
整理一下口供
Collate the statements.
与反恐指挥部核实所有证人身份 然后把他们放了
Verify all witness IDs with CTC and release.
怎么了 有什么问题吗
What? What is it?
没有 没问题 长官
No, nothing, ma'am.
控制台呼叫所有小队
Control to all units.
转为行动代号琥珀
We are moving to Amber.
目标人物涉嫌参与谋杀
Stand by for executive action to arrest the target
准备实施逮捕
on suspicion of conspiracy to murder.
目标人物必须显现出其有意图离开英国
The target must demonstrate intent to leave the UK.
所有在航站楼的逮捕小组 在出发层待命
Arrest teams at every terminal, remain inside Departures.
目标看到门口有武装警卫把守
Target sees armed guards at the door,
可能会因此而紧张 从而改变主意
he might get twitchy and change his mind.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标正经过M4高速3号匝道
Target passing M4 Junction 3.
盯住了 K9
Stay on him, Kilo 9.
你也许还不能逮捕他
You may not have power of arrest yet,
但你有尾随他的权利
but you have the power to stay up his arse.
了解
Understood.
抱歉打断一下 我需要这个房间
Sorry to cut this short. I need the room.
不必起身 汗女士 你可以留下
That's not necessary, Ms Khan. You can stay.
整理一下口供 跟反恐指挥部核实证人身份
Collate the statements. Verify witness IDs with CTC.
收到 长官
Yes, ma'am.
我要再看一遍采访
I need to see the interview again.
你知道怎么弄吗
Do you know your way round this?
我可是在隔音监控间做过的
Mm. I've spent my time in the gallery.
你问过我 赞达有没有接受过种族偏见测试
You asked me if Xanda had been tested for racial bias.
恐怕我的回答并不完全准确
I'm afraid my answer wasn't entirely accurate.
怎么了
What is it?
你还是认为王磊是幕后黑手吗
You still think Wanglei is behind this?
事实是
The truth is...
正是种族定性让赞达成为市场上
..racial-profiling is what makes Xanda the most effective
最有效的安全系统
security system on the market.
是呀 我当时想表达的是我对他投标并不支持
Yes, I was trying to withdraw my support for his bid.
他阻止我说中国会构成风险
He stopped me from saying China poses a risk.
但你「移花接木」后的视频中说
You were also corrected to say
赞达面部识别利用了种族定性
that Xanda Facial Recognition makes use of racial profiling.
大多数面部识别提供商认为定性属于人工智能缺陷
While most facial recognition providers see profiling as an AI flaw,
赞达将此视为一个卖点
Xanda treats it as a selling point.
作为赞达公司在英国的老大 他干嘛要让你这么说他们公司
Why would the head of Xanda UK make you say that about his own company?
我不知道 但他现在正想离开这个国家
I don't know, but he is currently trying to leave the country.
如果我们现在不阻止他 就再没机会问出答案了
If we don't stop him now, we'll never get the chance to ask.
T26呼叫K3
Trojan 26 to Kilo 3.
请讲
Go ahead.
按要求汇报人员的最新情况 长官
Update on asset as requested, ma'am.
他醒了吗
He's awake?
医生刚来检查过
Doctors just came to check him.
说他有希望一小时内醒来
Said they expect him to wake up in the next hour.
你说过要是他有情况 就呼叫你
You did say to call if he so much as stirred.
是 谢谢
Yes. Thank you. Ah...
怎么了
What is it?
K3呼叫K6
Kilo 3 to Kilo 6?
K6 请讲
Kilo 6. Go ahead.
你上次查看医院监控是什么时候
When did you last run a feed check to the hospital?
15分钟前
15 minutes.
现在看一下
Run another.
有什么问题吗 K3
Any concern, Kilo 3?
还不清楚
Unclear.
帕特里克家人在哪儿
Where's Patrick's family?
■
PPO
是伦敦警察厅保护司令部的一名官
员，负责保护英国王室成员、首相
、政府部长、大使、来访的国家元
首和其他被认为有危险的个人。
上次查看监控之前 个人保护官送他们回家了
PPOs escorted them home just before the last check.
我要过去看一眼
I'm heading back there.
查下监控 查一下安保人员
Check the feeds. Check the guard detail.
在2号频道向我汇报最新情况
Keep me updated on 2.
收到
Understood.
医院
Hospital?
正如我们讨论过的其他事宜一样 卡迪加
As with everything else we've discussed, Khadija,
这些都要保密
you keep this under wraps.
你给我提供深伪丑闻的新闻素材之前 我不会说出去的
Until you can give me everything, the deep-fake scandal.
是「移花接木」
Correction.
措辞方面交给我
You leave the wording to me.
我跟你一起去
I'm going to come with you.
不行 保护警察会送你回家
I-I can't allow it. The CPOs will take you home.
我刚对这起重大事件下达批示
I declared this critical incident.
如果有进展 我想知道详细情况
If there's a development I want to know what's going on.
坦白说 你是我唯一相信能告诉我真相的人
And, frankly, you're the only one I trust to tell me the truth.
别忘了这个 大臣 你会需要它的
Ah, don't leave this behind, Minister. You'll be needing it.
正如我所说
And, as I said,
只要你遵守承诺 我就会信守诺言
I'll keep my side of the bargain so long as you keep yours.
通讯检查 T21
Comms check, Trojan 21.
状态更新
Status update?
没有变化
No change, no change.
保护目标检查 一切正常
Asset check. All in order.
T26
Trojan 26.
没有变化 没有变化
R5. No change, no change.
病房安全 一切正常
Ward clear. All in order.
监控检查
Feed check?
T26 监控检查
Trojan 26, feed check.
一 二
One, two...
三
..three.
不好意思啊 T26
Unlucky, Trojan 26.
石头赢剪刀
Rocks beats scissors.
再来一次呗
Again?
监控检查完毕
Feed check complete.
K6呼叫K3
Kilo 6, Kilo 3.
医院监控检查 通讯检查 一切正常
Hospital feed check, comms check. All in order.
收到 每十分钟重复检查一次
Received. Repeat checks every ten minutes.
我马上过去
I'm on my way there.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标从M4高速4号匝道离开
Target exiting M4, Junction 4.
-确认 -确认
- Confirmed.  - Confirmed.
还有五分钟到达1号航站楼
Five minutes to Terminal 1.
控制台 我12分钟后抵达航站楼
Control, my ETA is 12 minutes.
在机场拘留嫌疑犯 等我到达
Detain the suspect at the airport and await my arrival.
收到
Understood.
你觉得我是不是弄错了
Do you think I've got this wrong?
如果不是中国
And if it wasn't China...
你为什么这么肯定内政部不会
What makes you so sure the Home Secretary wouldn't
正面回答有关王磊的问题
give us a straight answer on Wanglei?
英国正遭受可疑外国势力的攻击
The UK is under attack by a suspected foreign power.
你知道政府的反应是什么吗
Do you know what the Government's response is?
我也不知道
Neither do I.
我去找罗文·吉尔做简报的时候
When I tried to doorstep Rowan Gill for a briefing,
他让我回家休息
I was told to go home and rest.
他们在对你隐瞒着什么
What aren't they telling you?
西蒙
接吧
Take it.
我不知道该跟她说什么
Oh... I don't know what to tell her.
我不想撒谎
I don't want to lie.
我也不擅长这事
It's not really my area.
如果我们赢了
If we win,
你就能把所有事情都说给她听了
you'll be able to tell her everything.
控制台呼叫K1
Control to Kilo 1.
K1呼叫控制台
Kilo 1 to Control.
所有单位 准备行动
All units, stand by for executive action.
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标驶入转盘去往1号航站楼
Target taking roundabout exit for Terminal 1.
确认
Confirmed.
控制台呼叫K9
Control to Kilo 9.
一旦目标离开车辆
The minute the target is out of the vehicle
步行前往航站楼
and proceeding on foot to the terminal,
即构成出行意图
that is intent to travel.
就能过去实施逮捕
Walk up, hands on.
收到
Understood.
目标抵达1号航站楼
Target arrival at Terminal 1.
-确认 -确认
- Confirmed.  - Confirmed.
K9到达
Kilo 9, arrival.
多角度调取目标监控
Get more feeds on that target.
快点啊
Come on, then.
下车吧
Out you come.
K1呼叫控制台
Kilo 1 to Control.
确认目标仍处于监视中
Confirm eyes on target.
如指示 已派人跟住目标 GPS及监控同步布控
We have eyes on target. GPS and CCTV, as instructed.
盯的是目标人物还是目标车辆
Eyes on target or target vehicle?
盯的是目标
Eyes on target...
车辆
..vehicle.
操
Fuck.
确认一下 跟踪的是一辆窗户被遮住的外交车辆
To confirm, we have eyes on a diplomatic car with blacked out windows?
是的 自目标人物进入车内 就一直跟着
Yes, and we've had eyes on the same vehicle continuously
途中从未间断 K9
since the target got into it, Kilo 9?
确认
Confirmed.
那他为什么不出来呢
So why isn't he getting out?
K3呼叫控制台
Kilo 3 to Control.
请讲
Go ahead.
希思罗机场可能是调虎离山之计
Heathrow may be a distraction.
怀疑是声东击西
Suspected decoy operation in progress.
请求紧急派武装支援医院
Request urgent backup and firearms support to the hospital.
我两分钟后到
I'm two minutes away.
收到
Understood.
K3呼叫K6
Kilo 3 to Kilo 6?
K6 请讲
Kilo 6. Go ahead.
检查所有帕特里克·弗林警探的监控
Assume all feeds monitoring DS Patrick Flynn are unsafe.
监控一切正常 K3
Feed check all in order, Kilo 3.
K6 检查医院全部监控
Kilo 6, assume all hospital feeds are unsafe.
收到
Understood.
-帕特里克是 -格雷戈里·诺克斯袭击案中幸存的那位警官
- I take it Patrick is... - The surviving officer from the attempt on Gregory Knox.
他救了我同事的命
He saved my colleague's life.
他也是唯一见过嫌疑人的人
He's also the only eyewitness to the suspect.
控制台 后援大概多久后到
Control, what's the ETA on backup?
武装支援 三分钟后到
Firearms support, three minutes.
我现在去病房
I'll be on the ward.
不行 等待武装支援 K3
Negative. Stand by for Armed Support, Kilo 3.
这么做明智吗
Ah... Is-is that wise?
不等了吗
Not to wait?
我不是想教你该怎么做事 但是
I don't mean to tell you how to do your job, but...
那就好
Good.
想都别想
Ah. Don't even think about it.
在车上待着
Remain in the vehicle.
监控检查 病房检查 一切正常
Feed check. Ward check. All in order.
大楼安全
Building's clear.
等待支援
Stand by for support.
K3呼叫T21
Kilo 3 to Trojan 21.
请讲
Go ahead.
注意 总督察马上就到
Be advised, DCI incoming.
我在一楼 正在上楼
I'm on the ground floor, on the way up.
收到
Received.
这里安全 长官
You're all clear, ma'am.
凯里
Carey.
袭击前一天早上 我家门口停了辆货车
So there was a van outside my house the morning before the attack.
我们以为是狗仔 想偷拍
We thought it was, like, paps, trying to take our photos.
然后呢
So?
在这也出现了
Well, it's here.
同一辆货车 在拐角等着 没熄火
The same van, waiting on the corner, engine running.
别下车
Do not exit the vehicle.
T21 有生命危险
Trojan 21. Imminent threat to life.
T26 保护对象已暴露
Trojan 26. Asset compromised.
有生命危险
Imminent threat to life.
枪手在C区服务电梯里
Shooter is in the C Block service lift.
所有单位 进入未通知恐怖袭击紧急响应
All units. I need a PLATO response.
C区9楼 有生命危险
C Block, ninth floor. Threat to life.
重复 有迫切生命危险
Repeat. Imminent threat to life.
K3呼叫所有单位
Kilo 3 to all units.
控制台 能听到吗
Control, do you read me?
重复 保护对象暴露
Repeat. Asset compromised.
有迫切生命危险
Imminent threat to life.
枪手位于C区维修电梯中
Shooter is in the C Block service lift.
妈的
Oh, shit...
操你妈
Fuck you.
所有单位
All units.
警官遇袭
Officers down.
发生交火
Shots fired.
发生交火 警官遇袭
Shots fired. Officers down.
K3呼叫控制台
Kilo 3 to Control.
病房安全 保护对象正常 一切正常
Ward clear. Asset check. All in order.
所有单位
All units.
K3呼叫控制台 病房安全
Kilo 3 to Control. Ward clear.
保护对象正常 一切正常
Asset check complete. All in order.
T21 T26 完成检查
Trojan 21, Trojan 26. Check complete.
一切正常
All in order.
所有单位
All units.
警官遇袭
Officers down.
发生交火
Shots fired.
监控检查完毕
Feed check complete.
病房检查完毕
Ward check complete.
一切正常 结束
All in order. Over.
监控检查完毕 病房检香完毕
Feed check complete. Ward check complete.
一切正常 结束
All in order. Over.
K1呼叫控制台
Kilo 1 to Control.
我已抵达1号航站楼
Arrival at Terminal 1.
请更新状态
Status update?
没有变化
No change. No change.
K9能看到车辆 看不到目标
Kilo 9 has eyes on vehicle, no eyes on target.
确认
Confirmed.
你去敲一下车窗怎么样 K1
How do you feel about tapping on the window, Kilo 1?
哪个区
Which bay?
红区
Red.
红区没人啊
Red Bay is empty.
你说什么
Come again?
看不到目标车辆
No eyes on target vehicle.
控制台呼叫K1 我们看不到你 确认航站楼
Control to Kilo 1. We can't see you. Confirm terminal.
K1在1号航站楼
Kilo 1. Terminal 1.
出发层 红色卸客区
Departures, Red Bay drop off.
没有发现目标
No eyes on target.
也没发现目标车辆
No eyes on target vehicle.
也没看到K9
No eyes on Kilo 9.
K9 这里是控制台 你听到了吗
Kilo 9, this is Control. Do you read?
控制台呼叫K1 请确认目视目标
Control to Kilo 1. Please confirm visual on target.
控制台呼叫K9
Control to Kilo 9?
K9 确认位置
Kilo 9, confirm location?
K9 请回答
Control to Kilo 9?
K9呼叫控制台
Kilo 9 to Control.
目标由5号出口驶离M25公路
Target leaving the M25, Exit 5.
控制好跟踪距离 K9
Maintain that distance at your discretion, Kilo 9.
准备就绪后 汇报情况
Update when you're ready.
目标到达五橡岭
Target arrival at Five Oak Green.
开往家庭住址 预计两分钟到达
Home address, ETA two minutes.
K9 这里是控制台 听得到吗
Kilo 9, this is Control. Do you read?
K9 确认位置
Kilo 9, confirm location.
控制台呼叫K1
Control to Kilo 1.
吉玛
Gemma?
先锋行动失败
Operation Vanguard is compromised.
我这不算下车吧
I'm not exiting the vehicle.
这里是紧急响应中心 您需要什么服务
Emergency. Which service do you require?
警官 我叫艾萨克·特纳
Ah, police. My name's Isaac Turner.
我是内政部安全大臣
I'm the Security Minister for the Home Office.
我正在追捕一名嫌犯
I'm currently in pursuit of a suspect,
确切的说 是一群调查中的谋杀案嫌疑人
or group of suspects, in an ongoing conspiracy to murder investigation.
您位置在哪儿
What's your location?
我目前在黑福莱尔路
Ah, my location is the Blackfriars Road.
嫌犯开的是一辆面包车
The suspects are driving a van
车牌号GX66AEE 一辆高尔夫 车牌号X66AEE
with the registration GX66 AEE - that's Golf, X-ray, 66, Alpha, Echo, Echo.
他们正沿着黑福莱尔路往南开
They're driving south on the Blackfriars Road,
他们刚刚离开了医院
away from the hospital, which they've just left,
我确信
and where I believe that...
-好的 我马上安排调度 -哦 你们这么快就来了
- All right, I will dispatch... - Oh, you're here now.
我看到警车了
I can see a car.
-是你们吗 等等 -艾萨克 待在原地
- Wow. Was that you?  - Isaac, stay where you are.  One second.
别让自己陷入危险
And do not put yourself in any danger.
对 他们就在前面 灰色面包车
Yeah, they're up ahead. Grey van.
搞什么 你能跟他们说下吗 他们要
Oh, for fuck's sake, can you tell them? They're trying to...
艾萨克 可以重复下你的位置吗
Isaac, can you repeat where your location is?
搞什么
Fucking hell.
我没事 我正在报警 只想告诉他们
I-I'm fine. I've just got 999 here. I'm just telling them...
请下车 先生
Step out the vehicle please, sir?
不不 面包车朝那边去了 你得赶快追他们
No, no, the van is up there. If you don't go after them...
请下车
Please step out of the vehicle.
真是服了
Jesus Christ.
他们会修改监控的 然后逃之夭夭
They'll change the CCTV and get away.
请问你是车主吗 先生
Are you the owner of this vehicle, sir?
我是 什么 当然不是
Am I the... what? No, no, of course not.
知道你刚才车速多快吗
And are you aware of what speed you were driving at when we stopped you?
我
Am...?
你在逗我吧
You're shitting me.
手机数据和设置
已成功清除
整个系统都被搞垮了
The whole system was overwhelmed.
摄像头 网络 通讯
Camera networks, comms.
王磊根本没在去机场的路上
Wanglei was never en route to the airport.
他知道这样能引起我们的注意
He just knew it'd get our attention.
-不是他干的 -你说什么
- It isn't him.  - I'm sorry?
艾萨克·特纳呢 他安全吗
Where's Isaac Turner? Is he safe?
应该安全
Yeah, I believe so.
我还在等最新消息
I'm waiting for an update.
-他说他有个 -这里说话不方便
- Apparently, he says he got a... - We can't talk here.
如我所言 这里没有摄像头
There's no CCTV in here, like I said.
-也没有路由器 -谢了
- No routers.  - Thank you.
咱们先切断通讯和电话
Let's lose comms and phones, please.
可以帮我们保管一下吗
Would you mind keeping these safe?
不是中国干的
It's not China.
王磊只是被当做了诱饵
Just because Wanglei was used as a decoy
并不能说明他是同谋
doesn't make him complicit.
《新闻之夜》第二次被黑时
The second hack on Newsnight implicated Xanda
提到赞达使用了种族定性
in the use of racial profiling.
这有悖他的利益 也有悖北京的利益
That can't be in his interests, or Beijing's.
弗林病房的所有摄像头都连在独立安全的网络上
The cameras on Flynn's ward were isolated on a secure network,
由反恐指挥部七楼直接控制
controlled from the seventh floor of CTC.
知道 我们正在调查
We know. We're investigating.
行动组正在拆解系统 从头构建
Ops are tearing down the system and starting again.
这个幕后黑手正监视着我们的一举一动
Whoever's behind this is watching everything we do -
他们知道我们的下一步行动
they know our next move before we do.
他们黑进反恐指挥部 安全协议许可 BBC
They're into CTC, STRAP clearance, the BBC.
还进入了我们的安全通讯系统
They're into our secure comms,
竟然能伪造我们的声音 我天啊
and they're faking our own fucking voices, for Christ's sake!
你的重点是什么
What is your point?
我们认识的人之中 谁有这个级别的权限
Who do we know with that much access,
这么大的能力 能染指我们的一切
that much capability, with his claws into everything we do?
我见过他
I saw him.
弗兰克·纳皮尔
Frank Napier.
就在这个医院里
Here at the hospital.
弗兰克之前在这
Frank was here?
今晚早些时候 就在演播室被黑前
Earlier this evening, before the hack on the studio.
瑞秋 你有任何怀疑的理由都可以提
If you've got any reasoning, Rachel, let's hear it,
除了见过他 列举他的能力之外呢
beyond seeing the man here and listing his capabilities.
中情局在七楼没有眼线
The CIA does not have eyes on the seventh floor.
只要他们能找到黑进去的方法 就会去做
If they've found a way to hack into it, they do.
你也听到了
You heard him.
从弗兰克·纳皮尔的视角看 美国正陷入与中国的冷战
As far as Frank Napier's concerned, the US is in a cold war with China.
你觉得这是一场自导自演的假警报吗
You think this is a false flag operation?
由美国策划的
By America?
有可能
It's possible.
挑拨英国跟中国反目
A plot to turn the UK against China.
目前的消息太多太杂 用假警报行动解释不了
A false flag doesn't explain the mixed messaging.
还有别的
There's something else.
你说过演播室被黑意味着有内应
You said the hack on the studio gallery suggested inside help.
对
Yeah.
在调查演播室总监 视觉混合师
Well, while you're running checks on the director,
音效师的同时
the vision mixer, the sound man,
你还要考虑一个嫌疑人
there's another suspect you might want to consider.
他不在电视台工作
He doesn't work in TV.
也许倒是离我们更近一些
You might find him a little bit closer to home.
有权限操控演播室设备的
It wasn't just the crew who had access to
不止是电视台人员
the controls in that studio.
在我们的帮助下 纳皮尔团队中的一名核心成员
Thanks to us, a core member of Napier's team was given
有了完全没有限制的权限
a full unrestricted pass.
确切地说 是在你的帮助下
Or thanks to you, to be exact.
你到底想说什么
What are you driving at?
你是高级调查官
You're the SIO.
是你把纳皮尔的技术人员派进了BBC
You sent Napier's tech op into the BBC.
你处于震惊之中 警探
You're in shock, Detective.
我可以理解你此时的行为 不过也就到此为止了
That means you're entitled to be out of line, to a point.
也许你该回家休息下 之后我们再讨论这个问题
Perhaps we should discuss this after you've been home to rest.
这不难联系在一起
Well, it's hardly a leap!
如果弗兰克·纳皮尔真是幕后主使
If Frank Napier's behind this, you can't blame me
就别怪我怀疑你 甚至你们两个都有参与
for wondering if you are too. Both of you.
你他妈够了
Steady the fuck on.
一名警探死了
A Police Detective is dead.
两个武装人员死亡
Two firearms officers.
帕特里克本来不是目标
Patrick wasn't meant to be a target, though, was he?
他只是卷入了一场枪战 成了目击者
He got caught in the crossfire and became a witness.
一开始肯定没人想杀他
I'm sure no-one wanted him dead.
弗兰克·纳皮尔已经不是第一次牺牲英国人
But it wouldn't be the first time Frank Napier sacrificed
来掩盖「移花接木」了
British life for the sake of Correction,
你之前也没能阻止他 不是吗
and it wouldn't be the first time you failed to stop him.
够了
That is enough!
汉娜·罗伯茨是英国的敌人
Hannah Roberts was an enemy of the British State.
我需要知道
I need to know.
如果这是我们和中情局联手
If this is a plot between us and the CIA
想阻止英国政府使用中国科技
to steer UK government away from Chinese tech
那请告诉我
then I need to know,
至少帕特里克没有白白死掉
because at least then Patrick died for a reason.
我可以理解
I do understand.
如果
If, if...
如果北京参与英国面部识别领域
If Beijing gets a stake in UK facial recognition it could amount
就会带来深远的安全隐患
to a permanent security breach.
我们总归要阻止的
If we're not trying to stop that deal, we should be.
虽然连带牺牲了弗林警长
As hard as it is to take,
这很难接受 但我能理解
I understand if DS Flynn became collateral.
事关国家安全
It's national security.
虽然这想法充满爱国情怀
..as rousing as that was,
但你大错特错了
you couldn't be more wrong.
我们和你一样 都不知情
We're as much in the dark as you are.
我真的不相信弗兰克·纳皮尔跟七楼有关系
I seriously doubt Frank Napier has a hand in the seventh floor,
就算有 他也是孤军作战
but if he does he's on his own.
他一直都爱使些下作手段
He's a rogue player. Always has been.
你是在哪看见他的
Where did you see him exactly?
他在一楼
He was on the ground floor.
不知道是不是我恰巧看到的
I don't know if this was just for my benefit, but...
所以他也看见你了
So he saw you?
他好像是来医院办事的
He acted like he was here for something.
他去的是放射科
Radiology was the department.
天啊 瑞秋 他去放射科看病了
For God's sake, Rachel, the man had an appointment in Radiology.
这点我们可以证实吧
I'm sure we can verify?
弗兰克交给我吧
I'll deal with Frank. KNOCK AT DOOR
大臣
Minister.
你还好吗
Are you OK?
我没事
No, I'm fine.
我看到两个人开着一辆灰色奔驰面包车逃离医院
So I saw two men fleeing the hospital in a grey Mercedes van.
车牌号GX66AEE
Ah, GX66 AEE.
抱歉 你的信息很有帮助 但请告诉我
Sorry, this is all very helpful, but would you mind telling me
你为什么要来医院呢
what the hell you were doing here in the first place?
我坚持要来的
I insisted.
你没中枪真是个奇迹
It's a miracle you didn't get shot.
我们会送你去反恐指挥部
We'll get you to CTC,
录个完整口供
take a full statement.
不 抱歉 我没时间
No, I'm sorry. I haven't got the time.
内政大臣要见我
The Home Secretary has asked to see me, so...
弗林还好吗
Flynn?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你看到他们的样子了吗
Did you get a look at them?
嗯 他们都穿着刷手衣 带着口罩
Yes. They were both wearing scrubs and face masks.
但是能看得出来都是中等身材的白人男性
Well, I could see they were both white males, medium build.
其中一个大概一米八二左右
I'd say one was in the region of six foot.
另一个矮一点 大概一米七八
The other was smaller, about 5'10.
开始排查符合
Start processing hospital staff
这几个特征的医院员工
for anyone matching that description.
警探
Detective?
抱歉 我
Ah, sorry. I, erm...
我觉得你是对的 我需要休息
I think you're right. I do need to rest.
我明早再来
I'll be in in the morning.
你受了这么大的惊吓 你需要多休息一下
The shock you've had, you'll need longer than that.
给你算恩假吧
Consider it compassionate leave.
我们到时候再来讨论时间表的问题
We'll discuss timeline in due course.
谢了 长官
Thanks, ma'am.
长官
Sir.
■
辞职的呼声越来越高
看起来你今晚真够忙的
Well, it seems you've had quite the night.
你先是不和我 麦肯锡 或者新闻部门里的其他任何人
First you book yourself on the BBC without consulting me,
讨论就上了BBC的新闻
McKenzie, or anyone in the press department.
还下令要逮捕一名外国公民
You sanction the arrest of a foreign national whose only
他做过的不合理的事显然只有搭了车回家
apparent wrongdoing seems to be catching a ride home?
然后你被警察拦下来
And then you get yourself pulled over by the police for
因为你开着不是你自己的车超速
speeding in a car that isn't yours.
对 我支持了逮捕严王磊
Yes. I backed the arrest of Yan Wanglei.
现在我意识到警察找错地方了
Now I realise the police were looking in the wrong place
但是确实是有重大安全隐患的
but there was a major security threat.
当时感觉是正确的决定
At the time it seemed like the right decision.
这决定并不该你来做
It wasn't your decision to make.
嗯 说实话 我是担心如果你或者首相
Well, honestly, I was concerned if you or the PM had to make
必须对中国做出决策 你们会退步
a call on China, you would buckle.
真的吗
Really?
艾萨克 你是个聪明小子
Isaac, you're a clever lad.
你也看到晚间新闻的反应了
You've seen the reaction to Newsnight.
你知道让你来为了什么
You know where this is going.
我和首相谈过了
I've spoken to the PM.
抱歉 不 我不知道这会怎么发展
Sorry, no, I don't know where this is going.
你在电视上说你赞成种族定性
You sat on TV and said you were in favour of racial profiling.
什么
What?
没有别的选择啊
There's no other option.
我没这么说
I didn't say it.
你说了 我看了电视 我听到了
You did. I was watching and I heard you.
罗文 你知道是什么情况
Rowan, you know what's happening here.
他们黑进了采访 改了我的说辞
They're hacking my interviews and changing my words.
-也许不是中国 但是 -你没听我说
- Maybe it's not China, but... - You're not listening to me.
大家都听到了
People heard it.
现在这就是真的了
Now it's real.
欢迎来到这场「移花接木」的噩梦 艾萨克
Welcome to the nightmare that is Correction, Isaac.
现在我们的敌人在作假 我们又没法反驳
Now, our enemies fake things that we can't deny.
找不出证据
Proof is impossible.
没有证据的否认就没有意义
Denial without proof is pointless.
最糟糕的是
And, worst of all,
要是我们能证明或者否认 我们就完了
if we do ever prove it or deny it we are fucked.
为什么
Why?
你知道为什么 我们和他们一样有罪
You know why. We're as guilty of it as they are!
你也听到那些情报了
You heard those Intelligence spods.
「移花接木」曝光的话
If Correction unravels...
那反恐 法庭
..then Counter Terrorism, the courts,
司法部 全都会
the Justice Department, all unravels with it,
暴露在全球范围内
across the whole world.
对民主而言这更糟糕了
And it is worse in democracies
因为我们无法让法官或媒体闭嘴
because we can't muzzle our judges or our media
不去谈中国或俄罗斯 或任何该负责的人
like China or Russia, or whoever the hell did this.
内政大臣 我不会为我没说过的话道歉
Home Secretary, I'm not apologising for something I didn't say.
这已经不是道歉能解决的问题了
This has gone way beyond an apology.
你想让我辞职
You want me to resign.
麦肯锡觉得我们先行动的话 局面会更好看一点
McKenzie reckons it plays better if we make the first move.
你们要开除我
You're sacking me.
我们不会忘记你的
We won't forget this.
对吧 你只... 你需要花点时间
Right? You just... You need to just spend a...
等待洗清罪名 就这样
..a little time in purgatory. That's all.
-直到你能拿到 -我的第二次机会
- Until you get...  - My second chance.
这不是针对你
It's nothing personal.
我很抱歉 长官
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
我不知道 全程我都以为自己获取了最新情况
I didn't know. The whole time I thought I was getting updates.
不止你这么想
You're not the only one.
弗林警长那边 有人看到...
And DS Flynn, did anyone see...
没有 警探
Not here, Detective.
还没有
Not now.
有什么新任务吗 长官
What have you got for me, ma'am?
你首先需要做的是交出所有的手机和通讯工具
The first thing you need to do is hand over all phones and comms.
我们确认没问题之后 会给你替换
You'll be issued replacements as soon as we can guarantee they're secure.
明白
Ma'am.
我确实有任务给你
I do have something for you.
我们再谈
We'll talk.
妈的
Oh, for fuck's sake.
终于回来了 你一般都这时候下班吗
Finally! Is this what time you finish?
你怎么来了
Why are you here?
我给你打过电话
I called you.
我要借宿
I need to sleep over.
你说我什么时候来都可以
You said I could come stay any time, so...
听着 阿比盖尔 这
Look, Abigail, this is...
现在不方便 好吗
This is a bad time, OK?
我不能控制爸妈什么时候进城
I can't choose when Mum and Dad go on a city break.
怎么 你不能自己在家吗
What, and you can't be in the house alone?
我睡不着
I won't sleep.
你在这也没睡啊
You weren't sleeping here.
我是在等你
I was waiting up for you.
你在泡茶吗 我之前找不到燕麦奶在哪
Are you making tea? I couldn't find any oat milk.
要是没有的话不加也行
If you don't have oat milk, I'll do without.
我是说不用加奶 来点茶
The milk, I mean, not tea.
我喝茶就好
I'll have tea.
我有超多话想跟你说
I've got tonnes I need to talk to you about.
我开了个播客
I'm starting a podcast.
为什么不明天再说呢
Why don't we talk about it tomorrow?
别担心 现在你来了 我就能睡着了
Don't worry. I'll sleep now you're here.
家里被盗之后我就这样了 很奇怪
It's been like this since the burglary, which is weird
因为盗窃是在白天 我当时都不在家
cos that happened in the daytime and I wasn't even home.
这些天我自己想单独睡着
The only way I can get to sleep by myself these days
只能靠大麻
is when I vape weed,
但是我会在凌晨三点很焦虑地醒来
but then I just wake up at three in the morning with anxiety.
这是威士忌吗
Is this whisky?
你说啥来着
What did you just say?
我抽了大麻
I vape weed?
不好意思 你要逮捕我吗
Sorry, are you going to arrest me?
什么入室盗窃
What burglary?
就是入室盗窃啊
The burglary.
我以为爸爸已经告诉你了
I thought Dad would've told you.
什么时候的事儿
When was this?
我不知道 有几个月了
I don't know. Months ago.
你们几个月前被盗了 居然没人告诉我
You were burgled months ago and nobody told me?
我可是个警探啊
I'm a police detective.
爸爸估计是不想让你担心
Well, Dad probably didn't want to bother you.
我们知道你很忙
We all know how busy you are.
他们偷了什么
What did they take?
没偷多少东西 把我家翻遍了
Not a lot. They turned the whole place over
但是只偷了我的平板 还有妈妈的笔记本
but they only took my iPad, Mum's laptop...
-你要去哪儿 -我...
- Where are you going?  - I just...
我马上回来 你先睡吧
Ah, I'll be back soon. Just get some sleep.
等等 家里装警报了吗
Wait. Did they get an alarm?
入室盗窃之后 爸有没有装警报
After the burglary, did Dad get an alarm?
装了
Yes.
密码是多少
What's the code?
我的生日
My birthday.
告诉我具体的数字 阿比盖尔
You're going to have to tell me the numbers, Abigail.
艾萨克·特纳已被解除
Isaac Turner has been sacked from his role as
内政部安全大臣一职
Home Office Security Minister,
此前他在接受BBC采访时就种族定性
following comments he made during a BBC interview
发表过评论
about racial profiling.
而事实是 正是种族定性
The truth is, racial profiling is what makes Xanda
使赞达成为了世界上最高效的安保系统
the most effective security system in the world.
你能不能 把广播关了
Ah, could you, erm... Could you turn it off?
麻烦关掉吧
Just turn it off, please.
-我不是说一定是这样 但是 如果 -怎么了
- I'm not saying this is the case but if, say...  - OK?
-不 不 不 我 -17-35岁的穆斯林男性
- No, no, no. I... - ..Muslim men between the ages of
-最容易 -别担心 没事了
- 17 and 35 were the most likely to... - Don't worry. It's fine.
-在机场发起袭击 -嗯 谢谢你了
- ..launch an attack on an airport... - Yes, thank you.
把这些因素考虑在内的系统有什么问题
..what's wrong with a system that factors that in?
大臣 你是在说这个程序故意使用了种族偏向性吗
Minister, are you suggesting the programme uses racial bias deliberately?
停这儿 还是你想倒回去
Here, or you want to go back?
如果可以的话 我希望时间倒流
Back in time, if you could.
我觉得你说得对
I think you are right.
抱歉
I'm sorry?
你需要保护人民
You have to protect people.
你要辞去议员一职吗 特纳先生
Are you going to resign as MP, Mr Turner?
你的穆斯林选民凭什么给你投票呢
Why should your Muslim constituents vote for you?
特纳先生 你为什么不回应维多利亚·贝洛
Mr Turner, why won't you respond to the love-child allegations
关于私生子的指控
made by Victoria Bello?
"黑人的命也是命"的标志竟然出现在了我家门口
There are Black Lives Matter protesters out there.
-我不认为 -在我家外面抗议我的丈夫
- I don't think...  - Outside my house, protesting against my husband,
要是我没记错的话 他可是个黑人
who, last time I saw him, was black.
我还是黑人 西蒙
I'm still black, Simmy.
你为什么说那些话
Why did you say those things?
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
我问了你一个问题
I asked you a question.
是不是有人拿枪指着你脑袋逼你说的
Did someone put a gun to your head?
我的笔记本呢
Where's my laptop?
你的笔记本呢
Where's your laptop?!
我从昨晚11点就等着和你说话
I've been waiting to speak to you since 11 o'clock last night.
对 我很需要它
Yes. I need it.
我知道你有话要说 艾萨克
I know there are things you have to say, Isaac.
我旁观过那么多党内会议
I've sat through enough party conferences
看你像海豹一样对着你不喜欢的大臣
watching you clapping like a fucking seal for ministers you don't like,
你不支持的政策
for policies you don't truly believe in,
还有违背"你我为人"的政府立场鼓掌
government stances that don't always reflect who you are, who we are.
但是种族定性
But racial fucking profiling?
我现在不能说这个
I can't do this now.
你就不能和你妻子谈谈吗
You can't talk to your wife?
我整个晚上 整个早上
When I've spent all night, all morning,
都在想到底发生了什么 为你担心
wondering what the hell is going on, worrying for you,
告诉露比一切都好
telling Ruby everything's OK,
外面的人不是想伤害我们
that the people outside don't want to hurt us,
努力让哈里森远离电视
trying - unsuccessfully by the way -
顺便说一句 并没有用
to keep Harrison away from the TV?
对 没错
Yeah, that's right.
所以要是你不能和我谈
So if you can't talk to me,
那要不你去和你孩子们解释一下
then perhaps you'd at least like to explain to our children
为什么有人说他们的爸爸有种族歧视
why their daddy's being called a racist.
反正我不能
I certainly can't.
-我没有 -什么
- I didn't.  - What?
没说那些话
Say those things.
你什么意思
What does that mean?
你保证过回家后会给我解释的
You promised you'd explain to me when you got home.
我说的是 我能解释的时候再解释
I said I'd explain when I can!
那现在不行的话 什么时候行
Well, if not now, then when?
以防你没意识到 艾萨克
In case you haven't noticed, Isaac,
你已经丢了你在政府的工作 都结束了
you've just lost your job in government. It's over.
不 还没有
No, it isn't!
如果是弗兰克·纳皮尔搞的鬼
If Frank Napier's behind this,
你不能怪我怀疑你们俩
you can't blame me for wondering if you are too.
他你妈的够了
Steady the fuck on.
弗兰克·纳皮尔也不是第一次牺牲英国人
And it wouldn't be the first time Frank Napier sacrificed
来保护「移花接木」这个秘密了
British life for the sake of Correction,
你之前不也没能阻止他吗
and it wouldn't be the first time you failed to stop him!
够了
That is enough!
汉娜·罗伯茨是英国的敌人
Hannah Roberts was an enemy of the British State.
哈特承认汉娜·罗伯茨的参与
欢迎来到这场「移花接木」的噩梦 艾萨克
Welcome to the nightmare that is Correction, Isaac.
我们的敌人在作假 我们又没法反驳
Our enemies fake things which we can't deny.
找不出证据 没有证据的否认就没有意义
Proof is impossible. Denial without proof is pointless.
最糟糕的是 要是我们能证明或者否认
And, worst of all, if we do ever prove it or deny it
-我们就完了 -为什么
- we are fucked.  - Why?
你知道为什么 我们跟他们一样有罪
You know why. We're as guilty of it as they are!